<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coffee on Delicious Detector</title>
    <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/tags/coffee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coffee on Delicious Detector</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (C) 2014-2016 Delicious Detector; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://deliciousdetector.com/tags/coffee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Doppio - Hood River</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/doppio-hood-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/doppio-hood-river/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a nice coffee shop in Hood River, Oregon with high ceilings, and plenty
of indoor and outdoor seating. The wifi is strong and plenty fast enough for my needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s even right next to a sweet water fountain that dogs and kids like to cool off
in on hot days. Check out this place if you are looking for a good coffee
shop experience in Hood River.
Doppio is right next to the Hood River Distillery tasting room. The tasting room
was still being built out when I was there so it was not open for business yet.
Something to check out on my next visit to Hood River!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.doppiohoodriver.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.doppiohoodriver.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crows Feet Commons</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/crows-feet-commons-bend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/crows-feet-commons-bend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had my first lunch today at Wild Rose Northern Thai Eats. That place is awesome
and it was packed. I had the Khao Soi Curry. Really good stuff. I&amp;rsquo;m now at Crows
Feet Commons, and just finished my second lunch, a turkey and avocado sandwich on an Ocean Roll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been sitting here on the back patio staring out at the Deschutes River while my
dog lounges at my feet. Perfection. This is a classic place to visit here in Bend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crows Feet is the ultimate hybrid, and I&amp;rsquo;m in love with this place. They serve coffee,
craft beer, sandwiches, and even have a bicycle shop that sells accessories!
Now is a good time to mention that I need more places like Crows Feet in my life!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just met some long distance bicyclists as well. They needed some supplies for their ride
and knew this would be a good place to stop. They left Eugene, Oregon yesterday morning
and just arrived in Bend a few moments ago. Their plan is to keep riding east this summer
until they get too tired or the weather stops cooperating. The current goal for them
is Chicago, but they might shoot for Boston!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizen</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/citizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/citizen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been going to this place for years, and I love it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, that’s about all I can say because I love it so much. I can not risk having any
bearded hipsters overrunning this place!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.citizencoffee.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.citizencoffee.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Rococo</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/cafe-rococo-kirkland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/cafe-rococo-kirkland/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This medium size coffee shop in Kirkland deserves a special mention. They have
a lot of places to sit solo, or with a friend, and the wifi is really good too.
I only had one coffee there during my visit, but I really liked it. I also had
some food, which was surprisingly good for a coffee shop. The staff was really
helpful and friendly anytime I needed something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for the best coffee shop in Kirkland, this is probably it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rocococoffee.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.rocococoffee.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>