<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Delicious Detector</title>
    <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Delicious Detector</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (C) 2014-2016 Delicious Detector; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://deliciousdetector.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>2015 Travel Resume</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/page/2015-travel-resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/page/2015-travel-resume/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;january:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;January&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stevens Pass Ski Area, US-RT 2, WA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;february:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;February&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NW Demo Days at Mt. Bachelor Ski Resort&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sun River, Oregon&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bend, Oregon (Deschutes Brewing)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portland, Oregon (Hair of the Dog Brewing)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mt. Rainier National Park, WA (snow camping Mazama Ridge + Ski descent from Camp Muir)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;march:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;March&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Muir Snowfield, Mt. Rainier National Park, WA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;april:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;April&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington Pass, WA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Birthday Tour variation + Liberty Bowl, North Cascades National Park, WA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Winthrop, WA (Old Schoolhouse Brewing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;may:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;May&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Washington Pass, WA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cutthroat Bowl, North Cascades National Park, WA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Winthrop, WA (Old Schoolhouse Brewing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Orlando, Florida (Tasty Tuesdays in the Milk District)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boston, Massachusetts (Harpoon Brewing)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portsmouth, New Hampshire&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;june:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;June&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pinnacle Glacier, Tatoosh Range, Mt. Rainier National Park, WA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cle Elum, WA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bend, OR (Boneyard Beer, Oblivion Brewing, Bend Beer Co.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redmond, WA (Washington State Brewers Festival)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;july:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;July&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hood River, OR (Double Mountain Brewing, pFriem Beer, White Salmon Vineyard, Everybody&amp;rsquo;s Brewing)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timberline Lodge, Mt. Hood, Oregon (Ram&amp;rsquo;s head Bar)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ski descent from top of Palmer Snowfield, Mt. Hood, Oregon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;august:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;August&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spokane, WA (No-Li Brewing)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liberty Lake, WA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Squak Glacier, Mt. Baker/Koma Kulshan, WA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;september:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;September&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portland, Oregon (www.automacon.io)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New York, New York (UN General Assembly)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Muir Snowfield, Mt. Rainier National Park, WA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mason Lake, Alpine Lakes Wilderness, WA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;october:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;October&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everett, WA (Crucible Brewing)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Snoqualmie Pass, WA (DruBru Brewing Co.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OcTAYberfest 2015, skiing Paradise Glacier, Mt. Rainier National Park, WA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;november:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;November&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;San Francisco, California (Black Hammer Brewing, Local Brewing Co., 21st Amendment Brewing)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bellingham, WA (Aslan Brewing, Kulshan Brewing, Wander Brewing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Metcalf Moraine, Schriebers Meadow, Mt. Baker/Koma Kulshan, WA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;december:b5084a52f08549cda1583126c2b37509&#34;&gt;December&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Swift Creek, Shuksan Arm, Hwy 542, WA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Glacier, WA (Chair 9)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;North Bend, WA, (Banff Film Festival Tour)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alpental Ski Area, Snoqualmie Pass, WA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stevens Pass Ski Area, US-RT 2, WA&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crystal Mountain Ski Area, Hwy 410, WA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DruBru at Snoqualmie Pass Life</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/beer/first-drubru-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/beer/first-drubru-visit/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;first-impressions:a4dae080d730a90c32292774d737b92a&#34;&gt;First Impressions&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon pulling into the Pass Life parking lot DruBru is clearly visible.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doppio - Hood River</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/doppio-hood-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/doppio-hood-river/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a nice coffee shop in Hood River, Oregon with high ceilings, and plenty
of indoor and outdoor seating. The wifi is strong and plenty fast enough for my needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s even right next to a sweet water fountain that dogs and kids like to cool off
in on hot days. Check out this place if you are looking for a good coffee
shop experience in Hood River.
Doppio is right next to the Hood River Distillery tasting room. The tasting room
was still being built out when I was there so it was not open for business yet.
Something to check out on my next visit to Hood River!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.doppiohoodriver.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.doppiohoodriver.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kin - Hood River</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/kin-hood-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/kin-hood-river/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Watch out for new restaurant kinks here, especially around the service. Getting
good waitstaff in small towns is harder than good chefs. Be prepared for great
food, but questionable timing around your meal.
With a little polish, Kin will be a force to contend with in a town more known
for wind-boarding and breweries, rather than expertly prepared food and service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that Delicious Detector seeks out positive experiences as much as possible,
but aims to be transparent with regards to actual experiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To start off this post, Kin is a new Hood River joint that just opened in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The space is very nice, and they put some effort into the decor. Stepping into Kin
and hearing CCR on the sound system was giving me a really good vibe. I love CCR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was only one server on a holiday weekend Sunday brunch service. It was around
10am, so this was not shocking, as things might be winding down. However, service
was pretty slow, so I was alarmed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked no questions about the menu, I was really hungry too. When she brought some
water by I was ready to order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ordered two items:
* Waffle
* French toast&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did not think the above would overwhelm our server, or anyone for that matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a run down of the brunch experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only the waffle came out. We patiently waited for the French toast to follow.
When the chef commented that she was happy to see us eat all the grapes and blueberries
we replied that they were really good. She explained that some guests have been leaving
some of the fruit on the plate. I let her know that fruit is my thing, and that I’m
always looking for more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We then said we were looking forward to the French toast as well. Going off her
reaction, it was clear that our French toast was not even started to be prepared yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our server explained to us that the kitchen had misread her ticket. I think that
was BS. I’m not sure I saw her write anything down in my presence, so who knows
what really happened. I was really hungry, so I blacked out a few details during this mission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless, I find that unacceptable for I define as a slow Sunday morning at 10am.
Morning cobwebs in your head or not, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to screw up an order with only two items
and no modifications, but somehow this crew managed to do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only that kept us from paying and leaving when our French toast did not come
out was Creedance Clearwater Revival on shuffle play interspersed with other more current tunes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The waffle was fabulous. Very little syrup, and it seemed like pretty good quality
syrup, though maybe grade A. Grade B is the only way to go if you want real flavors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The French toast was actually on a French Roll, probably from the fabulous Knead
Bakery next store. A little crunchier than I prefer but it was good and I was
happy to get more of that good fruit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kineatery.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.kineatery.com/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yelp.com/biz/kin-hood-river&#34;&gt;http://www.yelp.com/biz/kin-hood-river&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knead Bakery</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/knead-bakery-hood-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/knead-bakery-hood-river/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kneadhoodriver.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.kneadhoodriver.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timberline Rams Head Bar</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/timberline-rams-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/timberline-rams-head/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First visit to the Rams Head Bar at Timberline Lodge, Mt. Hood Oregon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tray Fremont</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/tray-fremont/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/tray-fremont/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First visit to Tray, a new restaurant in the Fremont neighborhood of Seattle.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crows Feet Commons</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/crows-feet-commons-bend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/crows-feet-commons-bend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had my first lunch today at Wild Rose Northern Thai Eats. That place is awesome
and it was packed. I had the Khao Soi Curry. Really good stuff. I&amp;rsquo;m now at Crows
Feet Commons, and just finished my second lunch, a turkey and avocado sandwich on an Ocean Roll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been sitting here on the back patio staring out at the Deschutes River while my
dog lounges at my feet. Perfection. This is a classic place to visit here in Bend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crows Feet is the ultimate hybrid, and I&amp;rsquo;m in love with this place. They serve coffee,
craft beer, sandwiches, and even have a bicycle shop that sells accessories!
Now is a good time to mention that I need more places like Crows Feet in my life!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just met some long distance bicyclists as well. They needed some supplies for their ride
and knew this would be a good place to stop. They left Eugene, Oregon yesterday morning
and just arrived in Bend a few moments ago. Their plan is to keep riding east this summer
until they get too tired or the weather stops cooperating. The current goal for them
is Chicago, but they might shoot for Boston!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild Rose - Northern Thai Eats</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/wild-rose-bend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/wild-rose-bend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While in Bend I made sure to check out Wild Rose Northen Thai Eats for lunch.
The place was full even at 12:30. I was lucky to find a seat at the bar!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had their most well known lunch item, Khao Soi Curry. Egg noodles red onion and
pickled cabbage in a coconut curry broth topped with fried crispy egg noodles,
cilantro and lime. I had it with the tofu and it was really good!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really recommend Wild Rose if you are in Bend.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Bend</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/beer/in-bend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/beer/in-bend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After spending some time in Eastern Washington again, I decided that a trip to Bend was needed.
I had not been to Bend since NW Demo Days at Mt. Bachelor in February, and I barely got to spend any time in town on my last trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I arrived in town, I went immediately to Crux Fermentation Project and somehow
ended up with two flights of beer over the course of a couple hours.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasty Tuesday</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/tasty-tuesday-orlando/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/tasty-tuesday-orlando/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Always on the lookout for the best food experiences, my search brought me to
Orlando, Florida of all places. On a gorgeous May evening I arrived to one of
the best food truck rodeos I&amp;rsquo;d experienced in a long time! #TastyTuesday! Three
cool bars are all next to each other and they have a large variety of craft beer
and cocktails to enjoy with whatever food trucks catch your eye in the back
parking lot. I highly recommend checking this out if you are in Orlando or
visiting!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Search for &amp;ldquo;Tasty Tuesdays in the Milk District&amp;rdquo; on Facebook to find
the upcoming schedule and location. Just remember all the action is hidden
in the back, so don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you are in the right place. You will have a
great time!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Rococo</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/tavern-hall-bellevue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/tavern-hall-bellevue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a joint upstairs in the infamous Bellevue Square Mall. You have to enter
from the street on Bellevue Way, which makes it seem less &amp;ldquo;mall-ey.” I think I
just made up a word. You walk up some winding stair cases until you see some
windows. On the other side of said windows, it kind of looks like a scene from
an old 40’s movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My visit was during late lunch time. Their black bean burger was really good.
I don’t really like the vibe of this place, however, the bar top made of pennies
is really cool. The craft beer selection was pretty decent for a restaurant/bar
adjacent to a giant mall. The bartender was very cool. He told me that it turns
into a club or something night club&amp;rsquo;ish on the weekends. I think I just made up
another word again. I can’t even imagine who shows up to this place in the evening.
Perhaps it’s nicer than I’m imagining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bottom line:
Come here for the food and drinks, not the atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tavern-hall.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.tavern-hall.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizen</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/citizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/citizen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been going to this place for years, and I love it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, that’s about all I can say because I love it so much. I can not risk having any
bearded hipsters overrunning this place!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.citizencoffee.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.citizencoffee.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Rococo</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/cafe-rococo-kirkland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/cafe-rococo-kirkland/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This medium size coffee shop in Kirkland deserves a special mention. They have
a lot of places to sit solo, or with a friend, and the wifi is really good too.
I only had one coffee there during my visit, but I really liked it. I also had
some food, which was surprisingly good for a coffee shop. The staff was really
helpful and friendly anytime I needed something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for the best coffee shop in Kirkland, this is probably it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rocococoffee.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.rocococoffee.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014 Travel Resume</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/page/2014-travel-resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/page/2014-travel-resume/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;april-may:406d5a735d69548a6b178c24ce15800e&#34;&gt;April/May&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;~Costa Rica~&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Puntarenas&lt;br /&gt;
Santa Teresa&lt;br /&gt;
Malpais&lt;br /&gt;
Montezuma&lt;br /&gt;
San José&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;may:406d5a735d69548a6b178c24ce15800e&#34;&gt;May&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chicago, Illinois&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;june:406d5a735d69548a6b178c24ce15800e&#34;&gt;June&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;~New England~&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Boston, MA&lt;br /&gt;
Newburyport, MA&lt;br /&gt;
Plum Island, MA&lt;br /&gt;
Salem, NH&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;august-september:406d5a735d69548a6b178c24ce15800e&#34;&gt;August/September&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;~Espańa~&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Barcelona&lt;br /&gt;
Valencia&lt;br /&gt;
Buñol&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/La_Tomatina&#34;&gt;Festival de la Tomatina en Buñol&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;~Italia~&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Roma&lt;br /&gt;
Firenze&lt;br /&gt;
Siena&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;december:406d5a735d69548a6b178c24ce15800e&#34;&gt;December&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phoenix, Arizona&lt;br /&gt;
Blackcomb Glacier Provincial Park, Whistler, British Columbia&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>