<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drinks on Delicious Detector</title>
    <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Drinks on Delicious Detector</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (C) 2014-2016 Delicious Detector; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasting Notes</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/notes/tasting-2016-03-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/notes/tasting-2016-03-09/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;march-9th-2016:5354f2e796547a35da65b6d858d932e0&#34;&gt;March 9th, 2016&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;by Delicious Detector&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stopped by the 


&lt;a target=&#34;_blank&#34; href=&#34;http://www.thebeerjunction.com&#34;&gt;Beer Junction&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-external-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;


 on a cold and rainy
night to see what they were pouring. Here we go&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;three-magnets-old-skook-in-the-woods-barley-wine:5354f2e796547a35da65b6d858d932e0&#34;&gt;Three Magnets - Old Skook in the Woods Barley Wine&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Olympia, WA&lt;br /&gt;
12.5%&lt;br /&gt;
This is a pretty tasty barley wine. Especially considering the ABV&amp;hellip; There is not a lot going on flavor wise,
but I think that BJ is pouring this one a little bit too cold, if I&amp;rsquo;m being totally honest. I&amp;rsquo;m generally a
fan of barley wine and have a preference for the releases that Fremont has put out in recent times.
I&amp;rsquo;ve only recently heard about Three Magnets, and this is my first experience with any of their offerings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;two-beers-fall-line-russian-imperial-stout:5354f2e796547a35da65b6d858d932e0&#34;&gt;Two Beers - Fall Line Russian Imperial Stout&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seattle, WA&lt;br /&gt;
12% ABV&lt;br /&gt;
This is a great beer if you want something strong, smooth and dark. Very solid flavor. Would order again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;stone-brewing-americano-stout:5354f2e796547a35da65b6d858d932e0&#34;&gt;Stone Brewing - Americano Stout&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Escondido, Calif.&lt;br /&gt;
8.7% ABV&lt;br /&gt;
You&amp;rsquo;ll need a few sips to let this one settle on your palate. Once you are warmed up though, if you are
seeking an espresso / coffee flavor, this is a solid choice.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Hammer Brewing</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/black-hammer-brewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/black-hammer-brewing/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://instagram.fsjc1-3.fna.fbcdn.net/t51.2885-15/s480x480/e35/12677459_957590344325377_1792762794_n.jpg&#34;  /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;


&lt;a target=&#34;_blank&#34; href=&#34;http://blackhammerbrewing.com/&#34;&gt;Black Hammer Brewing&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-external-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;


 is a newer entry to the San Francisco Craft Beer scene. I made sure to check them out
during my visit, and I&amp;rsquo;m really glad that I did! Black Hammer is affiliated with 


&lt;a target=&#34;_blank&#34; href=&#34;http://www.pacbrewlab.com&#34;&gt;Pacific Brewing Laboratory.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-external-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;


&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be aware that at time of writing in November 2015, their brews are brewed in 


&lt;a target=&#34;_blank&#34; href=&#34;https://www.google.com/maps/place/Nevada&amp;#43;City,&amp;#43;CA&amp;#43;95959/@39.1650308,-121.3944321,9z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x809b7a7134408b49:0x37bfaa9a5ce0c3cd&#34;&gt;Nevada City, CA&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-external-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;



north of Sacramento. Black Hammer is waiting for the natural gas to be hooked up in this location at Bryant Street/Zoe Street in San Francisco when I visited. However, this location has been open for about three months now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bartender, &amp;ldquo;Scooter&amp;rdquo; was a really friendly guy and no joke, could pass for John Lennon easily.
The tap room had a cool vibe that reminded me subtly of some tap rooms in Seattle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really enjoyed the art they had displayed on all the walls too. A really nice touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tasting-notes:27cd252afa64e409ff89656819f18cfd&#34;&gt;Tasting Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hopportunistic #2&lt;/strong&gt; - 6.2% 34IBU&lt;br /&gt;
Citra dry hopped Extra Pale Ale&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;This is a good beer!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whipnose Imperial IPA&lt;/strong&gt; - 10% 88IBU&lt;br /&gt;
From Pacific Brewing Laboratory&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A solid effort, would order again&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Serendipitous Stout&lt;/strong&gt; - 7.7% 35IBU&lt;br /&gt;
Vanilla Chocolate Stout&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Seems like more vanilla than chocolate, though a tasty beer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bock Party&lt;/strong&gt; - 8.2% 23IBU&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Different take on a bock, but good!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nautilus Hibiscus Saison&lt;/strong&gt; - 5.3% 18IBU&lt;br /&gt;
From Pacific Brewing Laboratory&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a saison, but I still gave it shot.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;final-thoughts:27cd252afa64e409ff89656819f18cfd&#34;&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are in the area and looking for a cool place with something tasty that is not 21st Amendment, you should
check out Black Hammer. I have a feeling that their quality, which is already good, is going to go up when they start
brewing in their SoMa location here, so give them a shot!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;cheers,&lt;br /&gt;
Delicious Detector&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Brewing Co</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/local-brewing-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/local-brewing-co/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://scontent.cdninstagram.com/t51.2885-15/s480x480/e35/12728679_964382520306739_440541768_n.jpg&#34;  /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Since I was staying in the SoMa neighborhood of San Francisco, I decided to go for a walk to checkout a few places,
including &lt;a href=&#34;http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/black-hammer-brewing/&#34;&gt;Black Hammer Brewing&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/21st-Ammendment-Brewing&#34;&gt;21st Amendment Brewing&lt;/a&gt;
and here, 


&lt;a target=&#34;_blank&#34; href=&#34;http://localbrewingco.com&#34;&gt;Local Brewing Co.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-external-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;



The beer was pretty good and the space was large and amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;tasting-samples:33f7fcc8e623add248f5693da97aab2f&#34;&gt;Tasting Samples&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sutro Tower Stout 5.9% 59IBU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parklet ISA 4.7% 61IBU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Indian Summer Oktober Fest 6.3%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1776 India Black Lager 7.8% 73IBU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boomtown Brown 4.1% 23IBU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crooked Amber 5.6% 30IBU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;additional-thoughts:33f7fcc8e623add248f5693da97aab2f&#34;&gt;Additional Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Brewery seems like it&amp;rsquo;s an adjustment from the what the neighborhood has been like lately.
There is a &lt;strong&gt;HUGE&lt;/strong&gt; indoor sports center across the street, and I heard that it&amp;rsquo;s been sold recently.
Inevitably, the city block that the sports center comprises will most likely become street level retail
with condos or apartments above. This brewery is placed in perhaps the best location for such a development.
Though I&amp;rsquo;m sure that some in the neighborhood are not happy about this, such is progress&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boneyard Beer</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/boneyard-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/boneyard-beer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My first visit to Boneyard Beer in Bend! I finally made it!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://instagram.fsnc1-1.fna.fbcdn.net/t51.2885-15/s480x480/e35/12071229_545381622286097_187417345_n.jpg&#34;  /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;I have been enjoying Boneyard Beer for several years now, but a visit to the brewery itself has thus
far evaded me. I corrected that today&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I enjoyed several tasters samples and some great conversation with a few locals and visitors. The main
point of my visit was to try anything that I could not find anywhere else, but more importantly get
receive the infamous &lt;strong&gt;BONEYARD&lt;/strong&gt; stamp in my Delicious notebook. This was a pretty big deal for me because
so almost all brewing operations today have stamps for people on Ale Trails, etc. But their stamps are
usually so small!! I&amp;rsquo;m guessing this is to accommodate the various passports and maps in some manner
that is legible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally the producers of some of the best beers you can find anywhere are not interested in keeping
up with the Jones&amp;rsquo; when it comes to the size of their stamp!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Bend</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/in-bend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/in-bend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After spending some time in Eastern Washington again, I decided that a trip to Bend was needed.
I had not been to Bend since NW Demo Days at Mt. Bachelor in February, and I barely got to spend any time in town on my last trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I arrived in town, I went immediately to Crux Fermentation Project and somehow
ended up with two flights of beer over the course of a couple hours.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OOLA Distillery Tasting</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/oola-distillery-tasting-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/oola-distillery-tasting-notes/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday 5-21-2014, &lt;a href=&#34;http://downtownspirits.com&#34;&gt;Downtown Spirits&lt;/a&gt; in Seattle hosted a private tasting session for &lt;a href=&#34;http://ooladistillery.com&#34;&gt;OOLA Distillery&lt;/a&gt;. This was my first experience tasting the OOLA lineup. Alan from OOLA was the host for the tasting session and very informative. Alan was very knowledgeable about their products and processes for creating the entirety of their line up. Additionally, Alan was very responsive to my questions through out the tasting session. Thank you Alan!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of particular note before I go any further is that OOLA sources almost all of the materials for their lineup from Eastern Washington farms and from founder Kirby Kallas-Lewis’ home in Seattle. Things like Tuscan Blue Rosemary grow really well in Seattle, so for example rosemary from Kirby’s nearby home garden gets infused with their vodka to create OOLA Rosemary Vodka. Their product line truly is “local” whether looked at from the perspective of Seattle or Washington as a State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;tasting-parameters:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;Tasting Parameters:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All samples were served neat and poured into small shot glasses provided by Downtown Spirits. I also drank plenty of water between each new sample!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;oola-vodka:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;OOLA Vodka:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was very smooth and had much more flavor than I’m used to with Vodka. This features Washington grown organic winter wheat. A solid base for any special vodka cocktails in your repertoire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;oola-citrus-vodka:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;OOLA Citrus Vodka:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a standout of the tasting session. The locally grown Lemon Verbana really adds to this vodka. Highly recommended by Delicious Detector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;oola-gin:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;OOLA Gin:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This starts out with their Vodka as the base, and they build on top of that to create an excellent Gin. Use this for putting together excellent gin cocktails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;oola-cask-strength-waitsburg-bourbon-whiskey:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;OOLA Cask-Strength Waitsburg Bourbon Whiskey:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was another standout, but much higher proof then their standard. This comes in at 116-120 proof but still maintains a great consistency and drinkability. I would recommend this over a large ice cube or for the cocktail drinker in your life who likes them fierce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;oola-waitsburg-bourbon-whiskey:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;OOLA Waitsburg Bourbon Whiskey:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the highlight of the session for me as I really enjoy bourbon. It clocks in at 94 proof, and the toasting of their barrels really shine through. This was really smooth and easy to drink, a standout bourbon that should be sought out for use in cocktails or for enjoying over a large rock. Note that they season their barrels with bourbon sourced from another distillery, and it is described as blended on the bottle. This should not take away from your perspective of OOLA Bourbon. This is a quality product in every sense.
The following night after the tasting I found myself at one of my favorite spots, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.radiatorwhiskey.com&#34;&gt;Radiator Whiskey&lt;/a&gt; enjoying OOLA Bourbon Whiskey over a large ice cube. Absolutely delicious!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;overall-thoughts:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;Overall thoughts:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OOLA is doing some incredible things in a small space and in a very short time frame. For being so young of an operation, their product seems very mature and should go on your top shelf and be reserved for special occasions and friends who can appreciate a cocktail made with the finest ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;
Delicious Detector&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>