<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Skis on Delicious Detector</title>
    <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/ski/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Skis on Delicious Detector</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (C) 2014-2016 Delicious Detector; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://deliciousdetector.com/ski/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Whistler-Blackcomb Trip Dec 2014</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/ski/blackcomb-glacier-dec-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/ski/blackcomb-glacier-dec-2014/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;With some high pressure in the short term forecast I decided that a last minute
trip to Whistler was in order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-1:66c161c2e548e164804af4b1bdb4aca3&#34;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I arrived really late Friday night, so I opted for a half day pass on Saturday.
I rode up as high as I could on Blackcomb, but the lifts and rope tows were not
running to the Glacier. I decided to make my way out towards the summit of
Blackcomb Mountain. Much of the terrain was up here in early December was wind
effected from the first big winter storm that passed through. Traversing through
some deep wind deposits was proving difficult, but eventually I was able to make
my way up to a nice col just a little below the summit where I was able to de-ski
to setup a tripod and take some photos of the sun dipping below Black Tusk and
Whistler Mountain across the valley.
I love being the only one up in an amazing, beautiful zone like this.
With clouds starting to fill in the valley and the setting sun directly in
front of me on the horizon, this was a classic, you had to be there moment.
To summarize, it was epic. After spending a lot of time admiring my incredible
alpine surroundings, it was time to ski down! Being the last guy off the
backside of Blackcomb has it&amp;rsquo;s advantages on a day like this as there were very
few skiers that had ventured back here this day because the lifts were not running
to help folks get back here. Of course there was a lot of wind effected snow on
my way down. It was still nice to be skiing fresh snow after a long summer of
skiing on last years deposits. Some of the creeks in the lower valley on the way
back to the cat track were not fully frozen over yet, nor completely covered with
snow like they are later on in the winter. This added a little more time to my
descent, navigating through the short stretches of water as I made my way to the
cat track. I eventually had to navigate through some grooming machines that were
already starting their evening shift back on the front side of Blackcomb. I arrived
at the upper station of the Excalibur Gondola, which was still running. Naturally,
the gondola operator was a little surprised to see me, &lt;em&gt;though not too surprised.&lt;/em&gt;
The air was starting to get frigid by this time of the evening. When I was removing
one of my skis with my trusty K2 composite poles, the tip splintered into little
fragments, and now I was left with two tipless poles, the first one had splintered
long before on a previous outing some time ago!
Back at Whistler Village I popped into my corner room at Blackcomb Lodge Ltd. and
started out the evening with a Whistler Brewing Company Chestnut Ale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-2:66c161c2e548e164804af4b1bdb4aca3&#34;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ended up making my way into the edge of
Garibaldi Provincial Park, at the col that looks into the Fitzsimmons Creek drainage,
the start of the Spearhead Traverse. Some folks were camped way below me taking in the sunset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I was in Whistler I also made sure to pick up a 6 pack of Whistler Brewing
Company&amp;rsquo;s Chestnut Ale to give to my favorite ski tech back in Seattle. There is
something about this beer that I just love. While they call it Chestnut Ale, it
reminds me of butterscotch, it&amp;rsquo;s sooo good. Now some places you may find this beer
will just hand you bottle and want you drink out of it. I highly recommend that
you drink this one of out of a glass if you find yourself where they are serving
this in bottles, rather than on draught.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>