<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seattle on Delicious Detector</title>
    <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/tags/seattle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Seattle on Delicious Detector</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (C) 2014-2016 Delicious Detector; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://deliciousdetector.com/tags/seattle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Tray Fremont</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/tray-fremont/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/tray-fremont/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First visit to Tray, a new restaurant in the Fremont neighborhood of Seattle.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizen</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/citizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/citizen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been going to this place for years, and I love it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, that’s about all I can say because I love it so much. I can not risk having any
bearded hipsters overrunning this place!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.citizencoffee.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.citizencoffee.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2015 Washington Cask Beer Festival</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drafts/2015-washington-cask-beer-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drafts/2015-washington-cask-beer-festival/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damn The Weather</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/damn-the-weather-seattle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/food/damn-the-weather-seattle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some time in October 2014 I checked out Damn the Weather in Seattle’s Pioneer
Square. This was obviously before it was featured as a &amp;ldquo;Best new restaurant&amp;rdquo;
in Seattle Magazine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what you need to know:
The ice cubes there are from another planet. They are melted from the bottom up,
I shit you not. These cubes will make your cocktail experience one to remember
for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Food:
I had the sandwich with the egg placed into the bread itself. You want this.
Grilled romaine salad was pretty Damn Tasty too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://damntheweather.com&#34;&gt;http://damntheweather.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yelp.com/biz/damn-the-weather-seattle&#34;&gt;http://www.yelp.com/biz/damn-the-weather-seattle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was feeling hungry and adventurous, so after we left here we set out for
Kedai Makan on Capitol Hill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read more about that here:
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kedaimakansea.com&#34;&gt;http://www.kedaimakansea.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yelp.com/biz/kedai-makan-seattle&#34;&gt;http://www.yelp.com/biz/kedai-makan-seattle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OOLA Distillery Tasting</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/oola-distillery-tasting-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/oola-distillery-tasting-notes/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday 5-21-2014, &lt;a href=&#34;http://downtownspirits.com&#34;&gt;Downtown Spirits&lt;/a&gt; in Seattle hosted a private tasting session for &lt;a href=&#34;http://ooladistillery.com&#34;&gt;OOLA Distillery&lt;/a&gt;. This was my first experience tasting the OOLA lineup. Alan from OOLA was the host for the tasting session and very informative. Alan was very knowledgeable about their products and processes for creating the entirety of their line up. Additionally, Alan was very responsive to my questions through out the tasting session. Thank you Alan!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of particular note before I go any further is that OOLA sources almost all of the materials for their lineup from Eastern Washington farms and from founder Kirby Kallas-Lewis’ home in Seattle. Things like Tuscan Blue Rosemary grow really well in Seattle, so for example rosemary from Kirby’s nearby home garden gets infused with their vodka to create OOLA Rosemary Vodka. Their product line truly is “local” whether looked at from the perspective of Seattle or Washington as a State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;tasting-parameters:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;Tasting Parameters:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All samples were served neat and poured into small shot glasses provided by Downtown Spirits. I also drank plenty of water between each new sample!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;oola-vodka:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;OOLA Vodka:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was very smooth and had much more flavor than I’m used to with Vodka. This features Washington grown organic winter wheat. A solid base for any special vodka cocktails in your repertoire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;oola-citrus-vodka:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;OOLA Citrus Vodka:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a standout of the tasting session. The locally grown Lemon Verbana really adds to this vodka. Highly recommended by Delicious Detector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;oola-gin:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;OOLA Gin:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This starts out with their Vodka as the base, and they build on top of that to create an excellent Gin. Use this for putting together excellent gin cocktails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;oola-cask-strength-waitsburg-bourbon-whiskey:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;OOLA Cask-Strength Waitsburg Bourbon Whiskey:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was another standout, but much higher proof then their standard. This comes in at 116-120 proof but still maintains a great consistency and drinkability. I would recommend this over a large ice cube or for the cocktail drinker in your life who likes them fierce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;oola-waitsburg-bourbon-whiskey:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;OOLA Waitsburg Bourbon Whiskey:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was the highlight of the session for me as I really enjoy bourbon. It clocks in at 94 proof, and the toasting of their barrels really shine through. This was really smooth and easy to drink, a standout bourbon that should be sought out for use in cocktails or for enjoying over a large rock. Note that they season their barrels with bourbon sourced from another distillery, and it is described as blended on the bottle. This should not take away from your perspective of OOLA Bourbon. This is a quality product in every sense.
The following night after the tasting I found myself at one of my favorite spots, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.radiatorwhiskey.com&#34;&gt;Radiator Whiskey&lt;/a&gt; enjoying OOLA Bourbon Whiskey over a large ice cube. Absolutely delicious!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;overall-thoughts:dac93311d144963ad6e50d370b5eb9df&#34;&gt;Overall thoughts:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OOLA is doing some incredible things in a small space and in a very short time frame. For being so young of an operation, their product seems very mature and should go on your top shelf and be reserved for special occasions and friends who can appreciate a cocktail made with the finest ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers,&lt;br /&gt;
Delicious Detector&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>