<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beer on Delicious Detector</title>
    <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/tags/beer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Beer on Delicious Detector</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (C) 2014-2016 Delicious Detector; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://deliciousdetector.com/tags/beer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasting Notes March 9th, 2016</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/notes/2016-03-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/notes/2016-03-09/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;two-beers-fall-line-russian-imperial-stout:5354f2e796547a35da65b6d858d932e0&#34;&gt;Two Beers Fall Line Russian Imperial Stout&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12% ABV&lt;br /&gt;
This is a great beer if you want something strong, smooth and dark. Very solid flavor. Would order again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;stone-brewing-americano-stout:5354f2e796547a35da65b6d858d932e0&#34;&gt;Stone Brewing Americano Stout&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8.7%&lt;br /&gt;
You&amp;rsquo;ll need a few sips to let this one settle on your palate. Once you are warmed up though, if you are
seeking an espresso / coffee flavor, this is a solid choice.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Hammer Brewing</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/black-hammer-brewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/black-hammer-brewing/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://instagram.fsjc1-3.fna.fbcdn.net/t51.2885-15/s480x480/e35/12677459_957590344325377_1792762794_n.jpg&#34;  /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;


&lt;a target=&#34;_blank&#34; href=&#34;http://blackhammerbrewing.com/&#34;&gt;Black Hammer Brewing&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-external-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;


 is a newer entry to the San Francisco Craft Beer scene. I made sure to check them out
during my visit, and I&amp;rsquo;m really glad that I did! Black Hammer is affiliated with 


&lt;a target=&#34;_blank&#34; href=&#34;http://www.pacbrewlab.com&#34;&gt;Pacific Brewing Laboratory.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-external-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;


&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be aware that at time of writing in November 2015, their brews are brewed in 


&lt;a target=&#34;_blank&#34; href=&#34;https://www.google.com/maps/place/Nevada&amp;#43;City,&amp;#43;CA&amp;#43;95959/@39.1650308,-121.3944321,9z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x809b7a7134408b49:0x37bfaa9a5ce0c3cd&#34;&gt;Nevada City, CA&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-external-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;



north of Sacramento. Black Hammer is waiting for the natural gas to be hooked up in this location at Bryant Street/Zoe Street in San Francisco when I visited. However, this location has been open for about three months now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bartender, &amp;ldquo;Scooter&amp;rdquo; was a really friendly guy and no joke, could pass for John Lennon easily.
The tap room had a cool vibe that reminded me subtly of some tap rooms in Seattle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really enjoyed the art they had displayed on all the walls too. A really nice touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;tasting-notes:27cd252afa64e409ff89656819f18cfd&#34;&gt;Tasting Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hopportunistic #2&lt;/strong&gt; - 6.2% 34IBU&lt;br /&gt;
Citra dry hopped Extra Pale Ale&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;This is a good beer!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whipnose Imperial IPA&lt;/strong&gt; - 10% 88IBU&lt;br /&gt;
From Pacific Brewing Laboratory&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;A solid effort, would order again&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Serendipitous Stout&lt;/strong&gt; - 7.7% 35IBU&lt;br /&gt;
Vanilla Chocolate Stout&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Seems like more vanilla than chocolate, though a tasty beer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bock Party&lt;/strong&gt; - 8.2% 23IBU&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Different take on a bock, but good!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nautilus Hibiscus Saison&lt;/strong&gt; - 5.3% 18IBU&lt;br /&gt;
From Pacific Brewing Laboratory&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a saison, but I still gave it shot.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;final-thoughts:27cd252afa64e409ff89656819f18cfd&#34;&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are in the area and looking for a cool place with something tasty that is not 21st Amendment, you should
check out Black Hammer. I have a feeling that their quality, which is already good, is going to go up when they start
brewing in their SoMa location here, so give them a shot!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;cheers,&lt;br /&gt;
Delicious Detector&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Brewing Co</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/local-brewing-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/local-brewing-co/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://scontent.cdninstagram.com/t51.2885-15/s480x480/e35/12728679_964382520306739_440541768_n.jpg&#34;  /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Since I was staying in the SoMa neighborhood of San Francisco, I decided to go for a walk to checkout a few places,
including &lt;a href=&#34;http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/black-hammer-brewing/&#34;&gt;Black Hammer Brewing&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/21st-Ammendment-Brewing&#34;&gt;21st Amendment Brewing&lt;/a&gt;
and here, 


&lt;a target=&#34;_blank&#34; href=&#34;http://localbrewingco.com&#34;&gt;Local Brewing Co.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-external-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;



The beer was pretty good and the space was large and amazing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;tasting-samples:33f7fcc8e623add248f5693da97aab2f&#34;&gt;Tasting Samples&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sutro Tower Stout 5.9% 59IBU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parklet ISA 4.7% 61IBU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Indian Summer Oktober Fest 6.3%&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1776 India Black Lager 7.8% 73IBU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boomtown Brown 4.1% 23IBU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crooked Amber 5.6% 30IBU&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;additional-thoughts:33f7fcc8e623add248f5693da97aab2f&#34;&gt;Additional Thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Brewery seems like it&amp;rsquo;s an adjustment from the what the neighborhood has been like lately.
There is a &lt;strong&gt;HUGE&lt;/strong&gt; indoor sports center across the street, and I heard that it&amp;rsquo;s been sold recently.
Inevitably, the city block that the sports center comprises will most likely become street level retail
with condos or apartments above. This brewery is placed in perhaps the best location for such a development.
Though I&amp;rsquo;m sure that some in the neighborhood are not happy about this, such is progress&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boneyard Beer</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/boneyard-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/drink/boneyard-beer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My first visit to Boneyard Beer in Bend! I finally made it!&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://instagram.fsnc1-1.fna.fbcdn.net/t51.2885-15/s480x480/e35/12071229_545381622286097_187417345_n.jpg&#34;  /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;I have been enjoying Boneyard Beer for several years now, but a visit to the brewery itself has thus
far evaded me. I corrected that today&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I enjoyed several tasters samples and some great conversation with a few locals and visitors. The main
point of my visit was to try anything that I could not find anywhere else, but more importantly get
receive the infamous BONEYARD stamp in my Delicious notebook. This was a pretty big deal for me because
so almost all brewing operations today have stamps for people on Ale Trails, etc. But their stamps are
usually so small!! I&amp;rsquo;m guessing this is to accommodate the various passports and maps in some manner
that is legible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally the producers of some of the best beers you can find anywhere are not interested in keeping
up with the Jones&amp;rsquo; when it comes to the size of their stamp!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whistler-Blackcomb December 2014</title>
      <link>http://deliciousdetector.com/ski/blackcomb-glacier-dec-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://deliciousdetector.com/ski/blackcomb-glacier-dec-2014/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://deliciousdetector.com/media/epic-blackcomb-sunset1.JPG&#34;  /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;em&gt;Overlooking the Fitzsimmons Valley, Whistler Mountain, and Black Tusk on Day 2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-1:f8fb23129cf4204b760b8ecf7506af22&#34;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With some high pressure in the short term forecast I decided that a last minute
trip to Whistler was in order. We set out from Seattle at a pretty descent time.
Of course, I had been in the mood for some quality Vancouver fare the entire
drive up, so we stopped at one of my favorite places, &lt;a href=&#34;http://vijsrestaurant.ca/&#34;&gt;Vij&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt;.
It was a Friday night, as should be expected, we had to wait quite some time for
our table. The food and service was amazing and I&amp;rsquo;m always impressed at Vij&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We arrived really late Friday night, and checked in to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.blackcomblodge.com/&#34;&gt;Blackcomb Lodge Ltd&lt;/a&gt;.
I requested that the front desk not leave my skis out in the morning with everyone else&amp;rsquo;s and
they were really good about this. They put a special note on my skis, saying
&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;leave in locker&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;. I was very happy about this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-2:f8fb23129cf4204b760b8ecf7506af22&#34;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a late arrival on Friday, and a later start on Saturday morning, I wanted
a one-way lift ticket on Saturday to access the backcountry and Glacier. The
one-way lift ticket is a little known secret at WB. They do not seem to advertise it,
and I have never seen it mentioned on their web site. This is because it is considerably
less expensive than all the other lift tickets and passes they sell. Even noticeably
less than EDGE cards for WA and OR residents. Of course, there is also the simple fact
that since you are only riding the lifts one time, just to get to the Glacier,
it rightfully should in fact be noticeably cheaper than everything else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After waiting in line for what seemed like 15 minutes, the attending clerk would
not sell me a one-way ticket because I did not have my avalanche transceiver, probe and shovel
in my backpack at that exact moment in time. I asked the clerk if she had even read
the avalanche forecast for the day, and explained to her that there was no chance in
hell of a avalanche in the next 48 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;She proceeded to tell me that their strict policy at WB is to only sell one-way lift tickets to people that have **ALL** back country gear present and in their back pack at the time of sale, regardless of current weather conditions.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I then explained to her that is a shitty policy, and that I do not have time to
walk back to my room, grab the missing items, &lt;strong&gt;AND&lt;/strong&gt; wait in line again for another
15 minutes, noting that the missing items will just slow me down on my uphill skin anyway.
&lt;strong&gt;I have mountains to ski!&lt;/strong&gt; She then told me she would be happy to sell me a
half-day standard lift ticket at a price of $63.79 CAD. I asked her what the
difference in price is between that and the one way lift ticket, and from what
I remember, it was something like $10-$20 CAD. I told her that we wasted a lot
of time discussing the one-way ticket, and that she should have offered this option
to me much sooner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://deliciousdetector.com/media/IMG_1670-blackcomb-crop.jpg&#34;  /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;em&gt;On the way to the top of Blackcomb&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I rode up as high as I could on Blackcomb, but the lifts and rope tows were not
running to the Glacier. After skinning up the difference, I decided to make my
way out towards the summit of Blackcomb Mountain. Much of the terrain up
here in early December was wind effected from the first big winter storm that
passed through, but at least it was new snow!
Traversing through some deep wind deposits was proving difficult,
but eventually I was able to make my way up to a nice col just a little below
the summit where I was able to de-ski to setup a tripod and take some photos
of the sun dipping below Black Tusk and Whistler Mountain across the valley.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love being the only one up in an amazing, beautiful zone like this.
With clouds starting to fill in the valley and the setting sun directly in
front of me on the horizon, this was a classic, you had to be there moment.
To summarize, it was epic. After spending a lot of time admiring my incredible
alpine surroundings, it was time to ski down! Being the last guy off the
backside of Blackcomb has it&amp;rsquo;s advantages on a day like this as there were very
few skiers that had ventured back here this day because the lifts were not running
to help folks get back here. Of course there was a lot of wind effected snow on
my way down. It was still nice to be skiing fresh snow after a long summer of
skiing on last years deposits. Some of the creeks in the lower valley on the way
back to the cat track were not fully frozen over yet, nor completely covered with
snow like they are later on in the winter. This added a little more time to my
descent, navigating through the short stretches of water as I made my way to the
cat track. I eventually had to navigate through some grooming machines that were
already starting their evening shift back on the front side of Blackcomb. I arrived
at the upper station of the Excalibur Gondola, which was still running. Naturally,
the gondola operator was a little surprised to see me, &lt;em&gt;though not too surprised.&lt;/em&gt;
The air was starting to get frigid by this time of the evening. When I was removing
one of my skis with my trusty K2 composite poles, the tip splintered into little
fragments, and now I was left with two tipless poles, the first one had splintered
long before on a previous outing some time ago!
Back at Whistler Village I popped into my corner room at Blackcomb Lodge overlooking
Amsterdam Pub and started out the evening with a &lt;a href=&#34;http://whistlerbeer.com/&#34;&gt;Whistler Brewing Company&lt;/a&gt;
Chestnut Ale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;day-3:f8fb23129cf4204b760b8ecf7506af22&#34;&gt;Day 3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We rode lifts and skied on both Whistler Mountain and Blackcomb Mountain and did
the obligatory Peak-to-Peak ride early in the day. The snow conditions were only
mediocre as the lower halves of each mountain were barely covered, or not covered at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you could imagine, I wanted to get up as high as I could again to take advantage
of the newer snow. I headed out to the Blackcomb Glacier again in time for sunset,
and began the uphill skin again. With more time, I ventured out further than I had
the day before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ended up making my way into the edge of Garibaldi Provincial Park, at the col
that looks out to the rest of the Spearhead Range, the start of the Spearhead Traverse.
Some folks were camped way below me taking in the sunset. However, with no low
clouds hanging out in the Fitzsimmons Valley, the sunset would not be as incredible
as the previous day. I had timed things just right, yet again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://deliciousdetector.com/media/IMG_1733.JPG&#34;  /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;em&gt;skiers camped below on their first night of the Spearhead Traverse&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I de-skied at the top of the col separating drainages and went for a little walk up
and around to get a better view of some of the peaks I had been unable to see yesterday.
Of course as I was making my way around I noticed the faintest glimmer of movement
way out in the distance on a peak in the vicinity of Whistler Mountain. It was a skier
and split-boarder starting an amazing decent in wind deposited powder. Wow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back at my skis I was wishing that I was about to drop into wind deposited powder too :-(
Still, I had another fun and long ski descent in the last bits of light left in the day around 4:30pm.
Navigating the creeks down lower once again, I quickly made my way back to the Gondola
yet again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course for &lt;em&gt;après ski&lt;/em&gt; beers and dinner on our last evening we naturally had to
visit GLC, &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/garibaldiliftco&#34;&gt;Garibaldi Lift Company&lt;/a&gt;. We stayed
just long enough to catch the beginning of the show next door where the skiers and
boarders do jumps and maneuvers through hoops of fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I was in Whistler I also made sure to pick up a 6 pack of &lt;a href=&#34;http://whistlerbeer.com/&#34;&gt;Whistler Brewing
Company&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; Chestnut Ale to give to my favorite ski tech
back in Seattle. There is something &lt;a href=&#34;http://whistlerbeer.com/beers/valley-trail-chestnut-ale/&#34;&gt;about this beer&lt;/a&gt;
that I just love. While they call it Chestnut Ale, it reminds me of butterscotch (in a good way)
it&amp;rsquo;s sooo good. Some places you find this beer will just hand you a bottle and expect
you to drink out of it. I highly recommend that you drink this one of out of a glass
if you find yourself in that situation. The nose on this beer is so wonderful;
from a glass is a superior experience with this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recommended reading:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a target=&#34;blank&#34; href=&#34;http://opensnow.com/news/post/insider-s-guide-to-whistler-blackcomb&#34;&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://opensnow.com/news/post/insider-s-guide-to-whistler-blackcomb&#34;&gt;http://opensnow.com/news/post/insider-s-guide-to-whistler-blackcomb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>